Scott Shepherd

Creative Director, Project Manager, User eXperience Designer, Graphic Artist, and Front End Developer

> scott76shepherd@gmail.com 206.356.4695 LinkedIn scott-shepherd

Objective:

Full time employment on an Agile team

Introduction:

Being an owner/ partner at a startup for the past 3 years opened my eyes to all the various needs of a thriving business. My agency used an Agile philosophy to accomplish large and small projects. I performed many various roles from Client Manager, Product Owner, Scrum Master, Producer, to Delivery. Having vast knowledge of UX Design, Graphic Design, Marketing, and Software Development was critical in being able to communicate between all the intricate moving parts.

I am proficient with many software applications but have the most experience in the Adobe Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Experience Design, Premiere, Audition, and After Effects. I also have experience with HTML and CSS.

				•		
DΓ	/ ci	- 1-	\sim 1	14	\sim	
Po	JΙU	_ '	Οι	и	J.	

scotts.design

Recent Experience:

Creative Director and UX Designer at Solid State Pros

2015-2017: 1-2 years <u>www.solidstatepros.com</u>

As Creative Director I facilitated branding and UX projects with design teams.

Partners: Steve Haak and Stephen Morrissey

Creative Director, UX Designer, and Brand Strategist for NED Learning

2016-2017: 1 year <u>www.nedlearning.com</u>

As Creative Director I facilitated branding, character, graphic, and UX design on various

projects.

Partners: Stephen Morrissey and Timothy Kieran O'Mahony

Director of Media Productions at Solid State Pros

2015-2017: 2-3 years

As Director of Media Productions I scoped and executed media production projects.

Partners: Steve Haak and Stephen Morrissey

Graphic Designer at Solid State Pros

2015-2017: 2-3 years

As a Graphic Designer I produced multiple digital assets for SSP, from illustrations to vector

graphics.

Partners: Steve Haak and Stephen Morrissey

Education:

Bachelor of Science in Cognitive Psychology

Evergreen State College 2000-2003

http://evergreen.edu/

*This included computer science courses, logic, and discrete mathematics.

Bachelor of Arts in Media Production

Evergreen State College 2000-2003